YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
时间轴：加森
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： 非燕  阿蘅阿蘅  猫中之王  独醉
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： 怒海掀波YY猫  退出江湖赛太公    字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第八季  第六集
2012年的秋天
In the fall of 2012,
尼克和罗宾感情越来越好
Nick and Robin were going strong.
有时很难说究竟是什么
Sometimes it's hard to say what it is exactly
让一对情侣"琴瑟和鸣"
that makes a couple click.
妙极了
Bravissimo!
不管是什么  孩子们  尼克和罗宾
Whatever it was, kids, Nick and Robin
起初真的很合拍
really connected at first.
我觉得我们之间
Hey, you know, I think I'm really starting
好像真的有什么...
to feel something here..
但后来这种情况时常发生  他们开始渐行渐远
But then, as often happens, they started to drift apart.
为什么
Why?
谁知道呢
Who can say?
我和尼克都三天没做爱了
Nick and I haven't had sex in three days.
这全赖你
And it's your fault.
尼克不肯做爱
Nick won't have sex
是因为他拉伤了腹股沟肌肉
because he pulled his groin muscle,
都怪你让他加入白痴篮球队
all 'cause you made him join your stupid basketball team.
你刚才是说"白痴篮球队"吗
Did you say "stupid basketball team"?
-对  -天啊  伙计们
- Yeah. - Oh, my gosh, guys,
我们得赶紧把罗宾送去医院
we have to rush Robin to the hospital.
因为她把声带咽下去了
Because somehow, she swallowed her vocal cords
现在卡在直肠里
and they got lodged in her rectum,
所以她都用屁股说"屁话"
because she's talking out of her ass.
先驱广场娱乐中心
这个夏天  马修加入
Over the summer, Marshall had joined
一支市中心的职业篮球联盟
a midtown professionals basketball league.
他的律师队取名为"不可抗力"
His team of lawyers was called The Force Majeurs.
取自法律名词"force majeure"
自从他们输给了一支会计队
Ever since they lost to a group of accountants,
他就开始有点过于较真
he'd started getting a little intense about it.
你确定没偷用一两个职业篮球员吗  乔尔
You sure you didn't have a ringer or two out there, Joel?
不知道你在说什么
Don't know what you're talking about.
刚才的进攻真不错  阿布巴卡尔
Good hustle out there, Aboubakar!
如果乔尔能找人来冒名顶替  我们也可以
If Joel can use ringers, then so can we.
尼克是我们最优秀的球员
And Nick is our best player.
所以依我看来
So as far as I'm concerned,
你们俩都该"冷藏"下腹股沟
you can both keep your groins on ice.
"冰上腹股沟"吗
Groins on Ice.
麦迪逊广场最不受欢迎的假日节目
Least popular Madison Square Garden holiday show ever.
你为什么那么热衷于这个篮球联盟
Why are you so into this basketball league?
罗宾  这是30岁以上在市区工作人士的
Robin, it's the Little Ivies Professionals Over 30
小常春藤专业人员联盟
Who Work In Midtown League.
这可是玩真的
It's the show!
说来也有趣
You know, it's kind of funny,
想象下人们把冰块放在腹股沟上
imagining people icing their groins.
一开始会很凉很冰
I mean, first they'd be all cold,
然后冰会开始融化
and then the ice would start to melt, and
那里就会变湿  "大湿特湿"
things would get all wet and... steamy.
好了  莉莉
Okay, Lily.
听着  伙计
Look, buddy,
我也是"30岁以上在市区工作人士的
I'm also the captain of a team
小常春藤专业人员联盟"
in the Little Ivies Professionals Over 30
其中一队的队长
Who Work In Midtown League.
我也为那刺激感着迷
I'm addicted to the adrenaline, too.
不过  你不觉得你有点
Still, don't you think you're getting
太过痴迷于...
a little obsessive about...
打住  打住
Uh, hold up, hold up.
你刚是说你不但
Are you suggesting that you are
是篮球队的一员  而且还是队长吗
a member of a sports team and you're the captain?
说到"队长"
So says the "C"
我还把这个词缝到运动衫上了呢
I personally sewed onto my jersey.
我和维多利亚分手后
After Victoria and I broke up,
有空闲时间了
I had some free time.
所以我叫上了几个建筑师朋友
So, called up a few architect friends
组了个篮球队  名叫
and put together a little team called
"T字尺"[建筑师常用绘图工具]
the T-Squares.
看到了吗
See that?
地面不平
The floor's uneven.
那个窗户的设计也烂死了
And that window placement is rubbish.
如果精灵给我一个愿望
You know, if a genie gave me one wish,
我会拆掉那堵墙  然后重新整整
I would knock down that wall and create a nice flow.
好愿望
Great wish.
硬木太多了  对吧
I mean, there's too much hardwood, right?
你们这群书呆子到底打没打篮球啊
Did you nerds actually play any basketball?
我们这群书呆子  专注的是更重要的东西
Um, us nerds focused on something far more important:
感情凝聚
bonding.
你们肯定会被操傻了吧
You guys are going to get pounded.
而我却没那个福气
And I am not.
拜托  你几周不做爱都受不了吗
Oh, come on. You can't go a couple weeks without sex?
我们的控球后卫是个52岁的处男  快乐得很
Our point guard's a 52-year-old virgin, happy as a clam.
那他一定控得"一手好球"
I'm sure he's quite a ball handler.
问题是  现在我们不做爱
The problem is, now that we're not having sex,
就更多机会谈话
we're talking more,
而我发现尼克有点...
and I'm realizing that Nick is kind of...
蠢
dumb.
-真的吗  -不是吧
- Really? - News to me.
-我没注意到  -不
- I hadn't noticed that. - No.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你们也觉得他蠢吗
You guys think that he's dumb, too?
-蠢爆了  -脑子比气囊还空
- So dumb. - Air bags are sharper.
肌肉身材  肌肉脑袋
Hot as lava but just as thick.
你们什么时候开始注意到他蠢的
When did you guys start to notice that he was kind of dumb?
尼克在做字谜游戏的时候
Well, there was that time Nick was doing the crossword.
跟"Cut"同义的四字词是什么
Hey, what's a four-letter word for cut?
"cut"和"nick"都有切的意思
-尼克[Nick]  -什么事
- "Nick." - Yeah?
是与"cut"同义的四字词啊
Is a four-letter word for cut.
是什么
What is?
-"Nick"  -怎么了
- "Nick." - What?
知道了
Oh. I got it.
是"Shave"[五字]
"Shave."
"cut"和"shave"都有削的意思
还有他评论吉普赛人的时候
And there was the comment about Gypsies.
不不  我觉得吉普赛人现在
No, no. I think Gypsies prefer
更爱被叫做罗姆人
to be called Romani now.
是吗  真的吗
Do they? Really?
那独角兽  精灵
And what do unicorns and, uh, elves
和矮妖更爱被叫做什么呢
and leprechauns prefer to be called?
你知道吉普赛人
You do know, uh, Gypsies are
是真实存在的族群吧
a real ethnic group that actually exists?
伙计们  真是太惭愧了
Oh, you guys, I feel terrible now.
我一直以为他们是虚构的
I always thought they were just made up,
就跟地精  巨魔和海豚一样
like goblins or trolls or dolphins.
还有你说过  你跟尼克是怎样
And then there's that story you told about how you and Nick
搭上一个丹麦交换生
picked up that Danish exchange student
然后三人共浴的事
and you all took a shower together.
我从没说过那种事
I never told a story like that.
那现在可以说了
Well, no time like the present.
我们给那个丹麦骚货取个名字
Let's give this Danish ho a name.
就纳迪亚吧
I'm thinking Nadia.
对  这名字放荡不羁  而且性向不明
Yeah, she sounds slutty and bi-curious.
你到底怎么了
What is wrong with you?
你孩子就在那边
Your kid is right there.
要不要别这么黄啊
Maybe want to clean it up a lit...
你挂个宝宝  还练引体向上
You're wearing a baby and you're doing pull-ups?
不  泰德  我闲坐着等肌肉变软
No, Ted, I'm sitting around getting soft,
因为冠军"从不锻炼"
'cause that's what champions do.
问题是  现在我知道尼克有多蠢
The problem is, now that I know how dumb Nick is,
我得重新考虑这段感情
it's kind of making me reconsider the relationship.
为什么
Why?
最后  尼克的腹股沟会康复
Eventually, Nick's groin will heal
你们也会重登巫山
and you'll be back in Sexville,
重登巫山后  填字游戏只是浮云
where all the crossword puzzles only have one box to fill.
说到双重标准
Talk about a double standard.
每次我追不会看时间的大胸无脑女
Every time I go after a busty dullard who can't tell time
或以为我是莱昂纳多鬼魂的蠢妹
or thinks I'm the ghost of Leonardo DiCaprio,
我就被骂肤浅
I'm shallow.
但是罗宾却可以和一个
But somehow it's okay for Robin to date a guy
逛街时不能离开家长视线的蠢货
who can't be trusted around outlets.
甩了他
Dump him!
行了  太荒谬了
Okay, that is ridiculous.
尼克是天才吗  不是
Is Nick a genius? No.
他的智商有平均水平吗
But does he have average intelligence?
也没有
No.
但是他是一个人  有感情的人
But he is a human being, with a heart!
你是害怕  如果我甩了他  会影响到比赛
And you're afraid if I dump him, it'll throw off his game.
罗宾  上周他拿了36分和17个篮板球
Robin, he got 36 points and 17 rebounds last week.
那还是他球鞋穿错脚时的表现
And that was with his shoes on the wrong feet.
好吧  你们可能想知道
Well, you're probably all wondering
T字尺队现在是怎么训练的
how the T-Squares' practice went today.
T什么
The T-What?
我们用头脑比赛
We played up here.
其实人们并不知道
Basketball, people don't realize,
篮球关系到几何学  物理学和工程学
is all geometry, physics and engineering.
如果你像建筑家那样思考
If you think like an architect,
不用摸到球  就能赢一千场比赛
you could win a thousand games without ever touching a ball.
你的球怎么了
What happened to your ball?
隔壁的希伯来小孩会把球抢了
Some kids from the Hebrew school next door took it
而且不还我们
and wouldn't give it back.
和尼克的分手进行得如何了
How'd the breakup with Nick go?
那个...
Well...
我今天去找了算命师
So, I went to this fortune teller today
她说我身上有个诅咒
and she said there was a curse on me.
那她告诉你怎么驱除了吗
Did she sell you something to ward off the curse?
这你也猜到  你跟她一样神啊
It's like you're a fortune teller, too.
尼克
Nick, um...
我们得谈谈
I think we need to talk. Yeah.
就是...
Uh... it's just...
练得好结实
Whoa, these are hard.
反正这条五百元的手链
Anyway, this $500 bracelet will ward off evil
可以辟邪一周
till the end of the week, so...
你觉得你可以
Do you think that you could do,
边说话边做仰卧起坐什么的吗
uh, sit-ups or something while you talk?
可以啊
Yeah.
总之  这个算命师
Anyway, this fortune teller,
她仅从我的信用卡
she was able to tell me all sorts of stuff about my future,
社保号和驾照
just from my credit cards
就能预见我的将来
and my social security number, driver's license.
我就知道你会失败
I knew you'd cave.
所以为了让你和尼克分手
Which is why I came up with
我想出了一个激励你的方法
a little extra incentive to break up with Nick.
晚上八点分手  要么这个邀请生效
End it by 8:00 P.M. Tonight or this invite goes live.
"罗宾和帕特里斯的闺蜜玩乐日"
"Robin and Patrice's BFF fun day?!"
孩子们  帕特里斯是罗宾的同事
Kids, Patrice was a coworker of Robin's
她有点巴着罗宾不放
who'd become sort of obsessed with her.
罗宾一直到现在都设法
Robin had managed, until now,
和帕特里斯保持距离
to keep Patrice at arms length.
不过如果帕特里斯被邀请来参加
But if Patrice were invited to something called
"罗宾和帕特里斯的闺蜜玩乐日"
Robin and Patrice's BFF Fun Day,
她会一直粘着罗宾  绝不放手
she'd latch onto Robin and never let go.
你为什么这么做
Why would you do that?
马上删掉
Delete that right now!
不  我不给你点压力
No! If I don't give you a little push,
你就一直拖  拖到他能再登巫山
you'll let this drag on until Nick can have sex again,
到时候你又会在床上任他摆布  并继续拖延
and then you'll be right back to procrastinating on all fours.
不得不承认  穿西服的男士说得对
I hate to admit it, but the man in the suit has a point.
好吧  不过季后赛就快开始了
Fine, but the playoffs are coming up soon,
他可不能精神崩溃啊
and I can't have this guy an emotional wreck.
如果你要甩他  委婉点吧
If you do dump him, at least let him down easy.
对  带他去一家精致的餐馆
Yeah, take him to a nice restaurant.
最好是吃甜点的地方
Preferably a dessert place.
那样你就不必等吃完一顿饭
That way, you won't have to sit through a whole meal
才到...
before you get to...
-分手点  -正解
- Splitsville. - Exactly.
我说的是"分手甜品店"
No, Splitsville.
在街角的那个甜品店
It's a dessert place right around the corner.
分手的必去场所
It's sort of the place to end a relationship.
尼克  听我说
Uh, Nick, listen.
你是个很好的人
You are awesome
好到爆  但是我们...
and totally sweet, but we're just not...
你知道我要说什么  是吧
You know where I'm going with this, right?
不  不知道
No. No clue.
我觉得我们不该再"见面"了
I don't know if we should keep seeing each other.
你是想  关灯做爱  看不到对方吗
You want to start turning off the lights during sex?
不  天啊  不是
No. God, no.
不是  不是
No! No.
我觉得我们不太适合做情侣[我们不锻炼]
I am just worried that, as a couple, we're not working out.
你想一起去健身房吗
You want to start going to the gym together?
不是  尼克  事情是这样的
Okay, no, Nick, here is the deal.
对不起  亲爱的  接个电话
Sorry, babe. I got to take this.
抱歉
Excuse me.
喂
Hello.
怎么了
Hey, what's up?
你...
You...
什么...  我...
What? I...
我不明白
I don't understand.
不过你...
But you...
好吧  其实呢
Okay, um, you know what?
对不起  我得挂了
I'm sorry, I-I have to go.
怎么回事
What happened?
我...
I...
I, um...
抱歉  我不想说
Uh, I'm sorry, I can't talk about this.
对了
Anyway,
你刚想要说什么
what were you going to say?
我想说
Uh... I was gonna say,
你还想吃什么  随便点
order whatever else you want.
我请客[放在我身上]
It's on me.
谢了  不过我还是
Well, thanks, but I think I'd just rather
放在碗里吃吧
eat it out of a bowl.
你们还想知道
Well, no doubt you're all wondering
T字尺队第一场比赛是什么情况
how the T-Square's first game went.
什么队
What Squares?
想象一台完美协调的机器
Picture a well-oiled machine.
你的缝纫机吗
Your sewing machine?
时间只剩下两秒钟了
There were two seconds left on the clock.
阿布巴卡尔全力防守我
Aboubakar was all over me.
突然间我多年以来所受的建筑学训练
And that's when all my years of architectural training
成为了我的神助
came to my aid.
我看见了对手绝对发现不了的空隙
I saw the space in a way my opponents never would.
帅呆了
Yes!
我就说我会投进这种球的
I told you guys I'd make one of these!
结果  这个进球也被判无效
Turns out, those two points were taken away
因为他们说这球"出界"了
because apparently the ball went "out of bounds."
不过别担心
But don't worry,
我已经向联赛办公室申诉了
I'm appealing to the league office.
那个阿布巴卡尔  打完你们是一起冲澡吗
This Aboubakar-- I'm assuming you showered with the guy?
描述一下共浴的情景
Paint me a word picture.
你好
Hello.
莉莉  巴尼在吗
Lil, is Barney there?
他都不接电话
He's not answering his phone.
他现在有点小忙呢
Mm, he's a little busy right now.
是罗宾打来的
It's Robin.
37...  38...
37... 38...
打开免提放给我听  39
Put her on speaker. 39...
你什么时候变得如此孔武有力了
When did you start being able to do stuff like this?
几个月前  你连做个三明治
A few months ago, you had to catch your breath
都累得上气不接下气
after making a sandwich.
巴尼  快把"罗宾
Barney, delete the Robin
和帕特里斯的闺蜜玩乐日"的邀请删了
and Patrice's BFF Fun Day invite!
你和尼克分手没
Did you break up with Nick yet?
我分不了  他刚接了个特别不好的电话
I can't! He just got some horrible call.
我想大概是他家有亲戚死了之类的
I think a family member might have died or something.
太好了  太棒了
Oh! Yes! Yes!
一级好  一级棒
Yes! Yes! Yes!
我是说  罗宾没和他分手很棒
I mean, good that Robin can't dump him.
死人的事当然是很惨
The death part, less good.
罗宾  如果你和尼克分手
Robin, if you dump Nick,
他一怒之下  可能会把你上衣撕得粉碎
he could get mad and tear your blouse off.
然后一口咬在你脖子上
And then he bites you on the neck,
不是发狠地咬  而是介于
not super hard, just on the brink
快乐与痛楚边缘的那种咬
between pleasure and pain.
然后丹麦骚货纳迪亚
And then that Danish slut Nadia
冲入
bursts in...
你没时间了  他的腹沟伤马上就好了
You can't wait. His groin will heal
然后在不知不觉之间  你就会发现自己
and then before you know it, you'll be marrying a man
嫁给一个曾把香草味蜡烛都吃掉了的人
who once ate a vanilla-scented candle!
那件事错在我
That was on me.
我就不该把蜡烛放在厨房
I shouldn't have left it in the kitchen.
尽管那蜡烛还在烧  靠  这男的真蠢
Though, it was lit. Man, he dumb.
这份邀请将在五分钟后发送
The invite goes live in five minutes.
什么
What?!
这份邀请会自动发送  只有我能让它停下
It goes out automatically unless I stop it,
除非你在免提里甩了那个男人
and that only happens if I hear you dump Nick
否则我绝不按停
on speakerphone before then.
好吧
Fine.
尼克  抱歉抱歉
Hey, Nick. I'm sorry about that.
听我说
Um, listen,
有件事我需要
there's something I need
和你谈一谈
to talk to you about.
罗宾  抱歉  我刚没说完
No, Robin, I'm sorry. I'm like half here.
那通电话是
That phone call, it just...
我有坏消息要说
I got some really bad news.
我的医生帮我做了核磁共振图
My doctor did an MRI...
结果
and...
我的天  到底怎么了
Oh... Oh, God. What, what is it?
我的腹沟受伤情况比推测的严重
My groin injury is worse than they thought.
我好几周都不能打篮球了
I can't play basketball for weeks.
谢天谢地  我还以为他是要死了之类的
Thank God. I thought he was dying or something.
几周不能玩  到底几周不能玩
How many weeks? How many weeks?!
拜托  千万不要是
Please tell me it's not a tear
骼腰韧带拉伤
in the iliolumbar ligament.
我的骼腰韧带拉伤了
It's a tear in the "libioflumflar linament."
如果情况不严重  他还可以参加最后决赛
If it's a small tear, he can still make playoffs.
拉伤得相当严重
It's a big tear.
千万不要这一季都上不了场
He better not be out for the season.
-我这一季都上不了场了  -该死的
- I'm out for the season. - Damn it!
他们要独自对阵"算数能手"会计队了
They're going up against The Number Crunchers without me.
这不过是律师会计和爱缝纫的建筑师玩的
It's an after-work basketball league for lawyers
下班后篮球联赛
and accountants and architects who sew.
谁会这么看重这件事啊
I mean, who takes it that seriously?
老天爷啊
No...!
我只是不想让埃里克森教练失望
I just hate letting coach Eriksen down.
我愿意陪他一起上刀山下火海
I would follow that man through the gates of hell!
胜利
Winning.
几周前  当我们战胜了"算数能手"队时
What do we win when we beat those Number Crunchers
我们赢得了什么
a few short weeks hence?
一场比赛吗  这当然
A game? Sure.
一个奖杯吗  勉强算吧
A trophy? Sort of.
我们赢得了商店的25块礼品券
We win a $25 gift card to Bennigan's,
但我们真正赢得了什么
but what is it that we really win?
赢了比赛
The game!
-这我已经说过了  尼克  -是
- Yes, I said that Nick. - Right.
我们同时赢得了
But we also win
昂首阔步的权利
the right to walk tall.
赢得了敢于自称冠军的资格
The right to call ourselves champions.
所以我们要全力以赴
Yeah. So we are gonna go out and we are
把这群小会计打得溃不成军
gonna wipe the floor with those accountants!
赢得胜利之后  我们将会像君王一样
And afterwards, we will feast like kings
尽情享用西南铁板香料虾
on Southwest Fajitas and Cajun shrimp!
而饭钱  也会稍微地便宜一些
And that check, that check will be marginally less expensive!
-太好了  -太好了
- Yeah! - Yeah!
现在  他们大概不得不付全额的饭钱了
Now, they're probably gonna have to pay full price for that meal.
尼克  你人太好了  可我
Nick, you are so sweet, but I just...
好消息是
Good news is
反正我的腹沟都需要
it doesn't really matter if it takes my groin pull
长时间慢慢来恢复
a little longer to heal,
所以我又可以和你翻云覆雨了
so I may as well start having sex again.
我听着呢
Listening.
恶心着呢
Sickening.
狂奔出门着呢
Exiting.
尼克
Nick...
我只是
I just...
我
Ah... I...
你觉得如何
What do you think?
我觉得我突然想要来点火热的东西了
I think I am suddenly in the mood for something hot.
我懂了  看来我得点热的卡布奇诺了
I see. Sounds like I should order some cappuccinos.
明早之前都闭嘴别说话
Don't talk till tomorrow morning.
她不能和你一起回家  尼克
She can't go home with you, Nick.
-巴尼  -为什么呀
- Barney? - Why not?
因为罗宾和我深爱着彼此
Because Robin and I are in love.
巴尼  你来这里干什么啊
Barney, what are you doing here?
我是来解决某件
Taking care of something
你显然没法独自完成的任务的
you clearly can't do on your own.
抱歉
I'm sorry,
但你和罗宾没戏了
but you and Robin are done.
什么  罗宾  他什么意思
What? Robin, what is this?
巴尼  我知道你想干嘛
Barney, look, I-I know what you're doing, okay?
请别这样
Please stop.
罗宾不想伤害你的感情
Robin doesn't want to hurt your feelings
因为你这人不错
because you're a nice guy,
但她认为你很蠢  她讨厌你
but she thinks you're stupid and she hates you.
不用谢
You're welcome.
别这样
Stop doing this.
我爱她  尼克
I love her, Nick.
他不爱我
Look, he doesn't love me.
他这样说是因为...
He's just saying this because...
我爱她的一切
I love everything about her,
说出这种话  对我来说不容易
and I'm not a guy who says that lightly.
我这辈子对女人都是虚情假意
I'm a guy who has faked love his entire life.
我认为爱情只是
I thought love was just something
白痴才会有的感觉
idiots thought they felt,
但这个女人抓住了我的心
but this woman has a hold on my heart
就算我想挣脱也于事无补
that I could not break if I wanted to,
我不是没有试过摆脱对她的感觉
and there have been times that I wanted to.
我不知所措  任爱摆布
It has been overwhelming and humbling
有时甚至心里好痛
and even painful at times,
但我没办法不爱她
but I could not stop loving her
就如同不能呼吸一样
any more than I could stop breathing.
我无可救药地  义无反顾地爱着她
I am hopelessly, irretrievably in love with her.
而她却不知道我的爱有这么深
More than she knows.
罗宾  这是真的吗
Robin, is this true?
你也听到啦
You heard him.
哇  感觉我心里
Oh, wow, it feels like I have
有一块被拉伤的腹股沟肌肉
a pulled groin muscle in my heart.
-尼克  真是对不起  -别
- Nick, I-I'm so sorry.- Don't.
我只觉得也许...
I just think that maybe...
打扰下
Pardon me.
你刚刚也心碎了吗
But did you just also get your heart broken?
碎了
Yes.
刚刚我的心也碎了
I just got my heart broken, too!
那么你们两个
Well, do the... the two of you...
想去我家吗
...want to come back to my place?
-想  -走吧
- Yes. - Come on.
分手之秋就此结束了
Thus concluded the Autumn of Breakups,
-够疯狂的  对吧  -是啊
- Crazy, right? - Yeah,
知道什么是真正的疯狂吗
you know what would be really crazy?
如果他们一起上
If all of 'em got it on--
巴尼  罗宾  尼克  那两个女人
Barney, Robin, Nick, and those two women,
纳迪亚也带着宠物蛇
and you just know Nadia's watching in the corner
在角落看着
with her pet snake.
够了  你俩为什么不做爱
Okay, why aren't you two having sex?
什么
What?
说什么呢
Excuse me?
莉莉垂涎罗宾的性生活
Lily has been slobbering over Robin's sex life
就像卡通里流浪汉  垂涎窗台上变凉的馅饼
like a cartoon hobo watching a pie cool on a windowsill,
至于你
and you--
唯一一次你这样玩命地锻炼
the only other time you've ever exercised this seriously
是莉莉大一时患了单核血球增多症
was when Lily had mono freshman year
被我撞到你做单手俯卧撑
and I caught you doing one-armed push-ups
而你老弟下面摆着一碗冰
with your genitals over a bowl of ice.
你们什么时候开始禁欲的  为什么
So, when did you stop doing it and why?
就是从
It was, you know,
马文出生前开始的
before Marvin was born.
什么  这太离谱了
What? Th-That's insane.
生孩子后要禁欲一段时间
Well, you have to wait a while after having a kid,
然后又因为整晚照顾孩子而精疲力竭
and, and then you're exhausted from being up all night.
然后一种诡异的现象出现了
And then this uncanny phenomenon began.
你们得解决这个问题
Wow, you guys got to fix this.
没那么容易
It's not that easy.
泰德  有了孩子一切都变了
Ted, having a kid changes things.
没有时间  没有精力  永远没有二人世界
You don't have the time or energy, you're never alone.
给我
Come here.
你干嘛
What are you doing?
带马文出去散步
Taking Marvin for a walk
给你们一点私人空间
so you guys can have some privacy.
泰德  得了
Oh, Ted, come on,
这样解决不了问题
that's, that's just not the way that it works.
我们又不能说做就做
Yeah, it's not like we can have sex on cue.
我会给你们很多时间
Yeah, I'll give you guys plenty of time.
我甚至可能
Maybe I'll even
会顺路去体育馆  让马文看看
swing by the gym, show Marvin
他的泰德叔叔投出"神球"的地方
where his uncle Ted made "the shot."
如果我回来晚了
If I'm late,
那是因为有索要签名的人缠着我
it's 'cause I've been delayed by autograph seekers.
忘了马文的尿布包
Oh, forgot Marvin's diaper bag.
妈呀  快闪快闪
Yowza! Okay.
奥斯卡最佳虚假爱情宣言得主是
And the Oscar for Best Fake Romantic Speech
巴尼・斯丁森
goes to Barney Stinson.
我要感谢这么多年来  让我能够
I'd like to thank all the ladies over the years
练习虚假爱情宣言的所有女士
with whom I've practiced fake romantic speeches
当然了  感谢罗宾・特布罗斯基
and, of course, Robin Scherbatsky
对鱼水之欢没有抵抗力
for being so hypnotized by hog
所以我才有机会出马相救
that she needed me to come and save her.
知道吗  我不需要你来帮我
You know what? I didn't need your help.
你还差一点就要撕开他扣错纽扣的衬衫
You were this close to ripping off his misbuttoned shirt
扯掉他穿反的内裤
and pulling down his inside-out underpants.
不得不承认  你刚才演得很逼真
I'll give you this, you were pretty convincing.
耍白痴帅哥玩是我的强项
Hey, tricking good-looking idiots is kind of my thing.
不是
No.
我是说你的话  让人觉得是真心的
I mean, you were really convincing.
拜托  我只是救你这个兄弟出火坑
Please. I was bro-ing you out.
真庆幸他这么快就信了
I'm just glad he bought it so quick.
时间再久些  我就得吻你了
Any longer, I'd have had to kiss you.
喂
Hello.
我的神啊  罗宾  闺蜜玩乐日
Whoo, oh, my God, Robin, BFF Fun Day!
这是史上最美妙的事
That's the most amazing thing ever.
-你真懂我的心  -帕特里斯
- Like, you totally read my mind... - Hey, Patrice.
你收到了邀请  很好
Oh, you got the invite, great.
好的  我回头打给你
Uh, yeah, uh, let me call you back.
太好了  我都不能呼吸了
This is so fantastic, I can't even catch my breath.
好的
Mm-hmm, yeah.
知道我忘了做什么吗
You know what I forgot to do?
罗宾和帕特里斯的闺蜜玩乐日
T字尺队员  坏消息
T-Squares. Well, bad news.
联盟办公室有回音了
Heard back from the league office.
我的得分不能算
My shot is not going to count.
但人生有高有低嘛
But onwards and upwards, right?
小伙子们今天有啥想说的啊
What do you cats want to rap about, huh?
听着  教练  你很出色
Listen, Coach... you're great.
我们真的都很想继续做朋友
And we all really want to stay friends.
我可以改  我可以...
I can change, I can...
拜托  我们也有过开心的时候啊
Come on, we, we had some good times.
事情最近有些不顺
Things have been weird lately and...
是不是有新的建筑师出现了  老实告诉我
Is there another architect? Just tell me.